YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 7. Student Work
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. COMMITTEES
  - Personnel and Training Committee: minutes, 1961-68 (Box 744, Folder 22)
  - Task Groups
    - Christian Social Responsibility in the Field of Integration, 1956 (Box 744, Folder 23)
    - Financing the Christian Association, 1956 (Box 745, Folder 1)
    - Keeping Records and Making Reports, 1956 (Box 745, Folder 2)
    - on Native American Fund
      - General, 1970-72, n.d. (Box 745, Folder 3)
      - Reference materials, 1968-71, n.d. (Box 745, Folder 4)
- SERIES III. DEPARTMENT/DIVISION
  - Department policies, 1908-17 (Box 745, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - 1948-59, 1961-74, 1976-84 (Box 745, Folder 6-15)
      - 1985-99, n.d. (Box 746, Folder 1-6)
    - Southern region, 1969-70 (Box 746, Folder 7-9)
    - Odile Sweeney Memorial Fund, 1984-86 (Box 746, Folder 10)
  - Establishment of new student YWCAs
    - Inquiry summaries, 1979-91 (Box 746, Folder 11)
    - Inquiries: correspondence and notes,1973-98, n.d. (Box 746, Folder 12)
    - "New Work": correspondence and notes
      - General, 1966-83 (Box 747, Folder 1)
      - Boston Area, 1987-91 (Box 747, Folder 2)
      - Northwest, 1987-95 (Box 747, Folder 3)
      - Oregon, 1988-90, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 4)
      - Southeast
        - General, 1967-92, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 5)
        - New Orleans, 1968 (Box 747, Folder 6)
  - Reference materials
    - General, 1963-75, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 7)
    - "The Missing Student Project," University Religious Council, University of California at Berkeley, 1981 (Box 747, Folder 8)
    - South Africa and divestment, 1989-90, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 9)
    - Tourism, ethics of, 1985-89, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam, 1993-96, n.d. (Box 747, Folder 11)
  - Staff
    - General, 1954-66 (Box 747, Folder 12)
    - Meetings
      - Minutes and reports
        - 1922-23, 1926-32, 1934-40 (Box 747, Folder 13-17)
        - 1941-43, 1962, 1966, 1968-69, n.d. (Box 748, Folder 1-4)
      - Student Staff Convocation, Apr 1967 (Box 748, Folder 5-6)
    - Interracial Education Secretary job analysis, 1935-42 (Box 748, Folder 7)
    - Work plans and job descriptions, 1980-98, n.d. (Box 748, Folder 8)
- SERIES IV. CONFERENCES
  - General, 1910-84, n.d. (Box 748, Folder 9)
  - National Student Conferences
    - YWCA Women's Student Conference, Evanston, IL, Feb 1919 (Box 748, Folder 10)
    - Council of Christian Associations, Milwaukee, WI, Dec 1926-Jan 1927
      - General (Box 748, Folder 11)
      - Published report (Box 748, Folder 12)
      - Typed proceedings (Box 748, Folder 13)
      - Typed proceedings (cont'd) (Box 749, Folder 1-3)
  - National Student-Faculty, Detroit, MI, 1930 (Box 749, Folder 4)
  - Regional
    - Asilomar/Pacific Coast, 1914, 1925-32, 1961 (Box 749, Folder 5)
    - Geneva/Mid-West, 1912-67 (Box 749, Folder 6-14)
    - Middle Atlantic/Eagles Mere/East Central, 1913-46 (Box 750, Folder 1-2)
    - New England/Maqua/O-At-Ka/various locations, 1922-46 (Box 750, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Northwest/Seabeck, 1919-48 (Box 750, Folder 4)
    - Rocky Mountain/Western/Estes, 1913-49 (Box 750, Folder 5)
    - Silver Bay/Eastern/Northeast
      - General, 1905-38 (Box 750, Folder 6)
      - Recreation Committee notebook, 1907-11 (Box 750, Folder 7)
    - Southern, 1912-49 (Box 750, Folder 8-9)
- SERIES V. COUNCIL, [see also Organizations, YMCA and YWCA below]
  - General, 1925-62, n.d. (Box 750, Folder 10)
  - Rosters, 1985-98 (Box 750, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, reports, "Workbooks," and "Handbooks"
    - 1959-62 (Minutes and Reports) (Box 750, Folder 12-18)
    - 1962-1967 (Workbook) (Box 751, Folder 1-12)
    - 1968-72, 1974-75, 1977, 1980-81, 1984-95 (Box 752, Folder 1-16)
    - 1996-98 (Box 753, Folder 1-5)
  - Area/Regional Councils
    - General, 1960-94, n.d. (Box 753, Folder 6)
    - Regional Advisory Committee Chairmen: meetings, 1962-68 (Box 753, Folder 7)
    - Regional Development Committee Chairmen, 1968-69 (Box 753, Folder 8)
    - Asilomar (Pacific Southwest), 1922-40 (Box 753, Folder 9-12)
    - Eastern, 1968-72, [see also New England below] (Box 753, Folder 13)
    - Geneva (Mid-West/Central)
      - General
        - 1922-37 (Box 753, Folder 14-17)
        - 1938-72, n.d. (Box 754, Folder 1-6)
      - YM - YW relationships, 1939-40 (Box 754, Folder 7)
      - Publication: Ways That Work, n.d. (Box 754, Folder 8)
    - Middle Atlantic (aka East Central-central part of eastern region)
      - Eagles Mere, 1922-34 (Box 754, Folder 9-10)
      - Student Christian Movement of the Middle Atlantic Region
        - 1934 (Box 754, Folder 11)
        - 1935-41, 1965-69 (Box 755, Folder 1-2)
    - New England
      - Maqua (northern New England), 1922-25 (Box 755, Folder 3)
      - Maqua and New England, 1926-29, 1931-33 (Box 755, Folder 4)
      - Student Christian Movement of New England, 1933-54 (Box 755, Folder 5-7)
      - North East Regional Advisory Committee, 1965-69 (Box 755, Folder 8)
    - New York, 1966-69 (Box 755, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Northwest
      - Seabeck, 1922-24, 1927-41 (Box 755, Folder 10-12)
      - PNW Council of Christian Student Associations, 1935-55 (Box 755, Folder 13-15)
      - Joint YM-YW Regional Councils
        - 1950-52 (Box 755, Folder 16)
        - 1953-55 (Box 756, Folder 1)
      - PNW Advisory Committee, 1965-68 (Box 756, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Northwest and Pacific Southwest/Western, 1967-72 (Box 756, Folder 3-6)
    - Pacific Southwest, 1962-69 (Box 756, Folder 7)
    - Rocky Mountain/Inter-Mountain/West Central
      - Rocky Mountain Region Student Christian Movement, 1922-41 (Box 756, Folder 8-10)
      - Rocky Mountain Region Student YWCA, 1958-71 (Box 756, Folder 11-13)
    - Southern
      - 1922-25 (Box 756, Folder 14)
      - 1926-39, 1958, 1965-78 (Box 757, Folder 1-5)
    - South/Southwest: proposal for team staffing, 1968 (Box 757, Folder 6)
    - Southwest
      - General, 1922-31 (Box 757, Folder 7)
      - Southwest Council of Student Christian Associations/Hollister Joint Council, 1933-48 (Box 757, Folder 8-9)
      - 1954-70 (Box 757, Folder 10-11)
    - Western, 1989 (Box 757, Folder 12)
- SERIES VI. NATIONAL STUDENT ASSEMBLY (YWCA only), [see also National Student Assembly under Organizations,YMCA and YWCA below]
  - General
    - 1922, 1930, 1932, 1934, 1936-38, 1940, 1954-55, 1959, 1970, 1973 (Box 757, Folder 13-15)
    - 1976, 1977, 1979, 1980, 1982-83, 1985, 1986, 1988, 1989, 1991, 1992, 1994 (Box 758, Folder 1-15)
    - 1996, 1998, 2000 (Box 759, Folder 1-5)
  - Travel scholarship/Grants-in-aid, 1964-96 (Box 759, Folder 6)
  - "Songs and Worship," n.d. (Box 759, Folder 7)
- SERIES VII. ORGANIZATIONS
  - General
    - General and miscellaneous, 1916-64 (Box 759, Folder 8)
    - American Youth Congress, 1940-41, n.d. (Box 759, Folder 9)
    - Chinese Students' Christian Association in North America, 1948-51 (Box 759, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1945-59, n.d. (Box 759, Folder 11)
    - Council of North American Student Movements
      - General, 1913-23 (Box 759, Folder 12)
      - Minutes, 1912-20 (Box 759, Folder 13-15)
    - Federated Student Committee
      - General, 1921-28 (Box 759, Folder 16)
      - Minutes
        - 1923-26 (Box 759, Folder 17)
        - 1927-32 (Box 760, Folder 1-2)
    - International Student Service, 1938-39 (Box 760, Folder 3)
    - International Union of Students/Union Internationale des Etudiants, 1946 (Box 760, Folder 4)
    - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, 1945 (Box 760, Folder 5)
    - National Student Christian Federation
      - General, 1961-66, n.d. (Box 760, Folder 6-7)
      - Packet for January 1961 meeting (Box 760, Folder 8)
    - Student Christian Movement [U.S.], 1940-84 (Box 760, Folder 9)
    - Student Christian Movement in New England, 1936-65 (Box 760, Folder 10)
    - Student Christian Movement [International], 1909-57, n.d. (Box 760, Folder 11-12)
    - Student Volunteer Movement
      - General, 1941-89 (Box 760, Folder 13)
      - Convention and conference materials, 1910-24, 1951-56 (Box 761, Folder 1-2)
    - United States National Student Association, 1947-49 (Box 761, Folder 3)
    - United Student Christian Council, 1945-55, n.d. (Box 761, Folder 4)
    - World Conference of Christian Youth, 1939-52 (Box 761, Folder 5)
    - World Federation of Democratic Youth, 1945 (Box 761, Folder 6)
    - World's Student Christian Federation
      - General, 1920-87, n.d. (Box 761, Folder 7)
      - Histories, 1948-85 (Box 761, Folder 8)
      - American Provisional Council: minutes, 1938-43 (Box 762, Folder 1)
      - Conferences and Assemblies
        - Oxford, 1909 (Box 762, Folder 2)
        - Constantinople, 1911 (Box 762, Folder 3)
        - Lake Mohonk, 1913 (Box 762, Folder 4)
        - 1986-87 (Box 762, Folder 5)
      - European Student Relief
        - 1920-21 (Box 762, Folder 6)
        - 1922-25, n.d. (Box 763, Folder 1-6)
      - Report of a North American Working Party on "The Rise of China," 1968 (Box 763, Folder 7-8)
      - Student Friendship Fund
        - General, 1921-24, n.d. (Box 763, Folder 9)
        - Reports, 1922-27 (Box 763, Folder 10)
        - Executive Committee: minutes
          - 1921-23 (Box 763, Folder 11-13)
          - 1924-26 (Box 764, Folder 1-2)
    - World University Service, 1957-59, n.d. (Box 764, Folder 3)
  - YMCA and YWCA
    - Council of Christian Associations
      - General, 1924-31, n.d. (Box 764, Folder 4)
      - Conference materials, 1926-27, 1931 (Box 764, Folder 5)
      - Minutes and reports, 1923-34 (Box 764, Folder 6-12)
      - Christian World Education
        - General, 1928, n.d. (Box 764, Folder 13)
        - Committee: minutes, 1923-34 (Box 764, Folder 14-17)
      - Budget and Finance Committee, 1930-34 (Box 764, Folder 18)
    - National Intercollegiate Christian Council/National Student Council of the YMCA and YWCA
      - General and history
        - Miscellaneous, 1942-57, n.d. (Box 765, Folder 1)
        - "The NICC Record: What Does it Show?" by Betty Johns, 1951 (Box 765, Folder 2)
      - Precursor joint YMCA-YWCA meetings, 1934-35 (Box 765, Folder 3)
      - Annual Meeting [Councils], 1938-66, n.d. (Box 765, Folder 4-11)
      - Committees/Commissions
        - General, 1951-54 (Box 765, Folder 12)
        - Administrative Committee: minutes
          - 1936-40 (Box 765, Folder 13-15)
          - 1941-65, n.d. (Box 766, Folder 1-9)
        - Consultative Committee on Sex Values, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 766, Folder 10)
        - Ethnic Minorities Commission, 1936-41, n.d. (Box 766, Folder 11)
        - Interracial Commission, 1934-35 (Box 766, Folder 12)
        - Interracial Education Committee,1935-39, n.d. (Box 766, Folder 13)
        - Interracial-Intercultural Relations Committee, 1956 (Box 766, Folder 14)
        - Program Commission
          - Minutes, 1943-54 (Box 766, Folder 15-17)
          - Personal and Campus Affairs Committee, 1946-49 (Box 766, Folder 18)
          - Publications
            - General, 1943-52, n.d. (Box 767, Folder 1)
            - Program Pamphlets, 1944 (Box 767, Folder 2)
            - Program Papers, 1945 (Box 767, Folder 3)
            - Cabinet Workbook Program Papers, 1946-47 (Box 767, Folder 4)
            - Program Papers, 1948-51 (Box 767, Folder 5)
            - SPAN (Student Public Affairs News), 1945-54 (Box 767, Folder 6-7)
        - World Relatedness Committee, 1949-52 (Box 767, Folder 8)
      - Exchanges
        - European Work-Study Seminar, 1949-50 (Box 767, Folder 9-10)
        - Negro delegation to India, 1935-36 (Box 767, Folder 11)
        - U.S.A.-U.S.S.R. Student Exchange
          - General, 1958-59 (Box 767, Folder 12)
          - Scrapbook, 1964 (Box 767, Folder 13)
      - Interracial
        - Miscellaneous, 1939-41, 1961 (Box 767, Folder 14)
        - Inquiry on Racial Inclusiveness in Student YMCAs, YWCAs and SCAs, 1957-58 (Box 767, Folder 15)
      - Mailings
        - Dear Marion and Jack letters, 1943-44 (Box 767, Folder 16)
        - Cues, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 767, Folder 17)
      - National Student Assembly (YM+YW), 1941-41, 1946-47, 1951, 1954-55, 1956, 1958-59, 1962-63, 1967, n.d. (Box 768, Folder 1-5)
      - Publications
        - General, 1940-59, n.d. (Box 768, Folder 6-8)
        - Revolution and Response series, 1963 (Box 768, Folder 9)
        - Study booklets, 1954-55 (Box 768, Folder 10)
        - The Intercollegian
          - 1912, 1918-19 (Box 768, Folder 11-12)
          - 1919/20-1924/25 (Box 769, Folder 1-6)
          - 1925/26-1929/30 (Box 770, Folder 1-5)
          - 1930/31-1935/36 (Box 771, Folder 1-6)
          - 1936/37-1942/43 (Box 772, Folder 1-7)
          - 1943/44-1949/50 (Box 773, Folder 1-7)
          - 1950/51-1956/57 (Box 774, Folder 1-7)
          - 1957/58-1963/64 (Box 775, Folder 1-7)
          - 1964/65-1966/67 (Box 776, Folder 1-3)
      - Staff meetings, conferences, and seminars (joint YM-YW)
        - General, 1935-65, n.d. (Box 777, Folder 1-5)
        - National Seminar on Staff Development, 1959 (Box 777, Folder 6)
        - Staff Study Planning Committee, 1954 (Box 777, Folder 7)
        - Task Group on Ways of Work, n.d. (Box 777, Folder 8)
      - Training
        - Leadership, 1951, 1952, 1960 (Box 777, Folder 9-10)
        - Program planning, 1960 (Box 777, Folder 11)
      - World Affairs Consultation, 1953 (Box 777, Folder 12)
- SERIES VIII. PROGRAMS AND PROJECTS
  - General, 1958-94 (Box 777, Folder 13)
  - Projects Committee, 1964-67 (Box 777, Folder 14)
  - Appalachian Project: log, summer 1965 (Box 777, Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 777, Folder 16)
  - Danforth Foundation Pilot Program for Black University Women, 1972-73 (includes the publications "Career Planning for Black Women" by Juanita Papillon and Elizabeth Morgan) (Box 777, Folder 17)
  - Contemporary India, Seminar for American Student Leaders, Jun 1967 (Box 777, Folder 18)
  - East Los Angeles (proposed), 1984 (Box 778, Folder 1)
  - Experiment in Pluralistic Governance, 1974 (Box 778, Folder 1a)
  - Human Relations, [integration-related] 1966-67
    - Schiff Charitable Trust, 1959-63 (Box 778, Folder 2-4)
    - Field Foundation, 1965-67 (Box 778, Folder 5-6)
  - [The One] Imperative Model-Building Projects, 1970, 1974 (Box 778, Folder 7)
  - In-Service Training Program, 1949-50 (Box 778, Folder 8)
  - Intern Program, 1997, n.d. (Box 778, Folder 9)
  - International Experiences for Students
    - General, 1985-88, n.d. (Box 778, Folder 10-11)
    - Pacific Rim Student Project, Manila, summer 1989
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 778, Folder 12)
      - Applications (Box 778, Folder 13)
      - Reference materials and notes (Box 778, Folder 14)
  - Jacksonville Project: Desegregation of Schools, 1965 (Box 779, Folder 1)
  - Justice in America? Program and Action for Student YWCAs, 1971 (Box 779, Folder 2)
  - Pre-School Educational Enrichment (Hogg Foundation), 1966 (Box 779, Folder 3)
  - A Program Book for Student Christian Associations, 1948 (Box 779, Folder 4)
  - Race Relations Workshop, 1965 (Box 779, Folder 5)
  - Racial Desegregation and Integration in Colleges and Universities, 1956-57 (Box 779, Folder 6)
  - Rosebud Indian Reservation, 1965-66 (Box 779, Folder 7)
  - Student Program Models: solicitation letter and drafts, 1994-95, 1996, 1998 (Box 779, Folder 8-9)
  - Toward Pluralism: A Program to Alleviate Interracial Tension in Large University Residence Halls, Imperative Model-Building Projects, 1974 (Box 779, Folder 10)
  - Voter Education and Registration Project (New World Foundation), 1964-66, n.d. (Box 779, Folder 11-13)
  - Week Without Violence, 1995, 1997 (Box 780, Folder 1-2)
- SERIES IX. PUBLICATIONS
  - Miscellaneous, 1916-70 (Box 780, Folder 3)
  - Instructional pamphlets on committee and cabinet work, 1908-51 (Box 780, Folder 4-6)
  - Suggested Constitutions for YWCAs in Universities, Colleges, and Seminaries, 1908-17 (Box 780, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Board/Group pamphlets, 1933, 1942, 1964 (Box 780, Folder 8-9)
  - The Black Dispatch: publication of the Black Affairs Committee of the National Student YWCA, 1966-82 (Box 780, Folder 10-11)
  - Blurb Sheet, 1969 (Box 780, Folder 12)
  - Building for Freedom Today and Tomorrow pamphlet series, 1942-43 (Box 780, Folder 13)
  - College Voluntary Study Courses, 1915-20
    - First year, Second year (Box 780, Folder 14-15)
    - Third year, Fourth year (Box 781, Folder 1-2)
  - Discussion materials, 1923-46 (Box 781, Folder 3)
  - F.Y.W.I.: News'zine of the National Student YWCA,1996-98 (Box 781, Folder 4)
  - In the Company of Women: National Student YWCA Newsletter, 1985-94 (Box 781, Folder 5)
  - Interact: correspondence, 1969-73 (Box 781, Folder 6)
  - Interact, 1966-82 (Box 781, Folder 7-9)
  - Interracial News Bulletin
    - 1931 (Box 781, Folder 10)
    - 1932 (Box 782, Folder 1)
  - Interracial Programs of Student YWCAs by Yolanda Wilkerson, 1948 (Box 782, Folder 2)
  - Meditations, 1936-39, 1941 (Box 782, Folder 3)
  - National Student YWCA Highlights, 1973-74 (Box 782, Folder 4)
  - One YWCA: On the Campus-In the Community, 1958 (Box 782, Folder 5)
  - A Program Book and A New Program Book for Student Christian Associations, 1938, 1943, 1948 (Box 782, Folder 6)
  - Women: Partners of Men in the Home and the World. A discussion of the role of College-trained women in America today, 1955 (Box 782, Folder 7)
- SERIES X. REPORTS
  - Miscellaneous, 1912-62, 1999 (Box 782, Folder 8)
  - "An Analysis of the Undergraduate Representative System," Jan 1921 (Box 782, Folder 9)
  - "Annual Report of the Secretary for Interracial Education" by Yolanda B. Wilkerson, 1946-47 (Box 782, Folder 10)
  - "Position Paper on the Future of YWCA Work with Students," by Sara Kavich, 1978 (Box 782, Folder 11)
  - Committee Chair /Department Executive
    - Annual and biennial, 1910-21, 1956-94 (Box 782, Folder 12-13)
    - Periodic
      - 1906-23 (Box 782, Folder 14-15)
      - 1957-70 (Box 783, Folder 1-2)
    - Foreign/International Students, 1908, 1910-16, 1922, 1930-33 (Box 783, Folder 3-5)
    - Secretary
      - Convention, 1915-20 (Box 783, Folder 6)
      - Periodic
        - Adair, Helen M., 1920-21 (Box 783, Folder 7)
        - Allen, Hazel, 1921 (Box 783, Folder 8)
        - Babson, Helen, 1921 (Box 783, Folder 9)
        - Ball, Constance L., 1921-24 (Box 783, Folder 10)
        - Blanchard, Leslie, 1914-25 (Box 783, Folder 11-12)
        - Brady, Mabel G., 1919 (Box 783, Folder 13)
        - Bond, Caroline, 1919 (Box 783, Folder 14)
        - Brooks, Louise W., 1909-11 (Box 783, Folder 15)
        - Brown, Alice, 1921-22 (Box 783, Folder 16)
        - Bryson, Gladys, 1920-25 (Box 783, Folder 17)
        - Burner, Oolooah, 1911-22 (Box 783, Folder 18-19)
        - Burton, Margaret E., 1915-18 (Box 783, Folder 20)
        - Butler, Eliza R., 1910-19 (Box 783, Folder 21-23)
        - Cate, Dorothy, 1921 (Box 783, Folder 24)
        - Clark, Margaret Logan, 1921-22 (Box 783, Folder 25)
        - Conant, Ruth A., 1921-22 (Box 783, Folder 26)
        - Condé, Bertha, 1908-24 (Box 784, Folder 1-3)
        - Condon, Katharine, 1923 (Box 784, Folder 4)
        - Crandall, Lulu, 1922 (Box 784, Folder 5)
        - Curran, Doris, 1921-24 (Box 784, Folder 6)
        - Cutler, Ethel, 1908-19 (Box 784, Folder 7-9)
        - Dabb, Edith, 1909-21 (Box 784, Folder 10-12)
        - Dasef, Laura, 1921 (Box 784, Folder 13)
        - Derricotte, Juliette, 1918-24 (Box 784, Folder 14)
        - Donovan, Helen E., 1919-20 (Box 784, Folder 15)
        - Eckert, Bertha, 1921 (Box 784, Folder 16)
        - Erskine, Madeline, 1920-22 (Box 784, Folder 17)
        - Everett, Mabel T., 1909-15 (Box 784, Folder 18)
        - Fair, Helen Faye, 1921 (Box 784, Folder 19)
        - George, Katy Body, 1914-19 (Box 784, Folder 20)
        - Gerlach, Talitha, 1924-25 (Box 784, Folder 21)
        - Goforth, Caroline, 1921-22 (Box 784, Folder 22)
        - Gogin, Gertrude, 1920 (Box 784, Folder 23)
        - Gwin, Maude, 1923-25 (Box 784, Folder 24)
        - Hall, Deborah, 1921 (Box 784, Folder 25)
        - Halsey, Katharine C., 1921-24 (Box 784, Folder 26)
        - Hamilton, [Julia] Mae, 1921-23 (Box 785, Folder 1)
        - Heller, Elsie B., 1921-25 (Box 785, Folder 2-3)
        - Heyneman, Ruth M., 1921 (Box 785, Folder 4)
        - Hitchcock, Harriet, 1924-26 (Box 785, Folder 5)
        - Holloway, Cecelia, 1910-12 (Box 785, Folder 6)
        - Holmquist, Louise A., 1909-12, [see also Department Executive reports] (Box 785, Folder 7)
        - Hoyt, Alice G., 1920-24 (Box 785, Folder 8)
        - Hunter, Lucy, 1918 (Box 785, Folder 9)
        - Hunton, Addie W., 1914 (Box 785, Folder 10)
        - Inskeep, Mildred, 1921-22 (Box 785, Folder 11)
        - Klenk, Frieda, 1921-23 (Box 785, Folder 12)
        - Lawson, Elizabeth, 1921 (Box 785, Folder 13)
        - Lealtad, Catharine, 1918-19 (Box 785, Folder 14)
        - Loucks, Grace, 1920-24 (Box 785, Folder 15)
        - Lumpkin, Katherine DuPree, 1921-25 (Box 785, Folder 16-17)
        - Lutters, Marie, 1920 (Box 785, Folder 18)
        - Meek, Susie S., 1919-21 (Box 785, Folder 19)
        - Miller, Flora J., 1910-11 (Box 785, Folder 20)
        - Moss, Miriam D., 1921-22 (Box 785, Folder 21)
        - Nelson, Amanda C., 1919-20 (Box 785, Folder 22)
        - Pearson, Ruth Lee, 1919-20 (Box 785, Folder 23)
        - Perry, Frances L., 1921-26 (Box 785, Folder 24)
        - Pierce, Florence M., 1921-23 (Box 785, Folder 25)
        - Pinyon, Josephine, 1912-16 (Box 785, Folder 26)
        - Reid, Rebecca, 1921-25 (Box 785, Folder 27)
        - Richards, Katharine L., 1920-22 (Box 785, Folder 28)
        - Riggs, Lucy Y., 1921-25 (Box 785, Folder 29)
        - Ross, Elizabeth A., 1908-10 (Box 785, Folder 30)
        - Saddler, Juanita, 1921-23 (Box 785, Folder 31)
        - Salisbury, Helen V., 1918-19 (Box 785, Folder 32)
        - Scudder, Mary Theresa, 1919 (Box 785, Folder 33)
        - Scurlock, Stella, 1924 (Box 785, Folder 34)
        - Seesholtz, Anna, 1918-19 (Box 785, Folder 35)
        - Sharp, Agnes A., 1919-20 (Box 785, Folder 36)
        - Stone, Mabel A., 1918-20 (Box 786, Folder 1)
        - Stuart, Marguerite, 1921 (Box 786, Folder 2)
        - Thomas, Helen L., 1912 (Box 786, Folder 3)
        - Thomson, Henrietta, 1924 (Box 786, Folder 4)
        - Webb, Betty, 1925 (Box 786, Folder 5)
        - Weisel, Mary E., 1920-22 (Box 786, Folder 6)
        - Wilbur, Theresa, 1909-10 (Box 786, Folder 7)
        - Williams, Clayda J., 1922 (Box 786, Folder 8)
        - Williams, Frances, 1921-25 (Box 786, Folder 9)
        - Wygal, Winnifred, 1921-23 (Box 786, Folder 10)
        - Yarrow, Millacent, 1919 (Box 786, Folder 11)
        - Young, Willie [or Willa] R., 1921-25 (Box 786, Folder 12)
      - Staff Quarterly
        - Bigsby, Marjorie, 1978-83 (Box 786, Folder 13)
        - Kavich, Sara, 1975-78 (Box 786, Folder 14)
        - Logan, Kay W., 1983-85 (Box 786, Folder 15)
        - Lundy, Mary Ann, 1982-86 (Box 786, Folder 16)
        - Redenbaugh, Eula, 1978-81 (Box 786, Folder 17)
        - Santiago, Joan Blaustein, 1984-85 (Box 786, Folder 18)
        - Serrano-Lux, Frances, 1979-82 (Box 786, Folder 19)
- SERIES XI. STUDENT ASSOCIATIONS AND REGISTERED STUDENT GROUPS
  - General
    - "General," 1914-96, n.d. (Box 786, Folder 20)
    - Notebook of historical information about College and University Associations (by region), circa 1930-1961
      - Geneva, Middle Atlantic, New England, New York (Box 786, Folder 21-24)
      - Pacific Northwest and Southwest, Rocky Mountain (Box 787, Folder 1-2)
    - Registered Student Groups, 1950-96, n.d. (Box 787, Folder 3)
    - Student Associations and Registered Groups, lists, 1950, 1966-67, 1974-96, n.d. (Box 787, Folder 4)
    - Lists, 1979-98, n.d. (Box 787, Folder 5)